
Speaker 1  (00:00)
Continuing rest yeast, we're growing east on the pv tour. We come to another really great park. This is another park that is right along the side of the block creek. 

Speaker 1  (00:14)
It is a fence off area and that is a protected ecosystem. Remember so that no people going inside of the creek area itself, but you get to hear the frogs, watch the birds and just enjoy being really close to some nice nature between Los Angeles feels really nice. There's also a great playground as a little kid's playground and a bigger kid's playground with Little Rock climbing setups. 

Speaker 1  (00:39)
And one of those monkey bars and spinny things, and then there's one of the largest world trail elements called a pull up bars, different types of pull up bars as well as some pushup bars, so you can really work, your upper body, your chest, your arms and there's also a small bathroom. It's actually not that small, it has 4 bathrooms and the watering fountain and cleaning hands. And there's some nice nice picnic areas. 

Speaker 1  (01:11)
Multiple separate picnic areas. And then this right here is one of The Crown. Jewels of pyovista, which is the main playa vista soccer field, and this is where the club teams come and they have to reserve it and I sell it installed. 

Speaker 1  (01:27)
It is a professional artificial turf. Modern installation has like a layer of sand and asphalt under there or something. And I don't know. 

Speaker 1  (01:37)
I'm going to do more research on the court here because it is a real piece of work very, very, very expensive field to be installed. It took a long time and they maintain it beautifully. And yeah, this is continuation of the trail, so there's dog bags available as well. 

Speaker 1  (01:55)
These nice little wooden structures that provide shade, just interesting, kind of sculpture, geometric wooden sculptures, and then there's the next dog park in pliovista. The third of our tour, this is the one I call the bubble park, because it has as a feature. 2 large hills inside of it, and there are artificial and of course the grass is artificial with this one as opposed to overrider, where it's wood chips and it has a stream going through the middle of it starting at the water fountain and going across the other side, dogs really like to lie in it. 

Speaker 1  (02:30)
But also yearn it in it, and many do observe that this arc sanitary issues may occur because of its feature that is close to, you know, the dogs are urinating, and then sometimes they're getting in there. And that's not great. But it's a beautiful, I love it anyway. 

Speaker 1  (02:51)
The dogs love to run up-and-down the 3 hills, not 2 and there's a nice shade structure and benches. And it's just very nice and Again, another victim of the pickleball war is 2 tennis courts that were permanent tennis courts. Now featured 3 permanent pickleball courts. 

Speaker 1  (03:07)
So we've lost even more permanent tennis courts in favor of permanent pickleball courts. Yep, so that's the way it's going these days to just people like to play pickleball. And so that's this portion, I think this might be called the bluff creek park. 

Speaker 1  (03:24)
And yeah, that's that. 
