
Speaker 1  (00:01)
The pv walking tour This is the first stop the apply. Mr. Walking tour, which is the concert park? 

Speaker 1  (00:10)
It is right at the main entrance. Which is concert park drive off of Washington? One of the main ways into the pioneer neighborhood. 

Speaker 1  (00:18)
There's a large bathroom facility here, and a lot of picnic benches all around the edges and it's the main village of pia vista coffee shops, Bodega, grocery store, a few restaurants, all the sorts of things like that. And it's kind of the heart of I guess you could say westplie of vista. 
