
Speaker 1  (00:02)
This is concert or excuse me, this is Crescent park, this is a park which reminds me of New York City in some strange ways. Because it's parks, surrounded by all apartment towers and they're not really towers in a New York way, but they are taller than a lot of what you'll see around this part of Los Angeles 564 story buildings, and it's a nice long park in the shape of a long Crescent, I suppose, and it has ample parking both sides of the street on the street that goes all the way around it. 

Speaker 1  (00:39)
So this is often a hidden spot to find parking for the sports park and for the Westchester, the bluff creek. It's a belovedly bluff creek trail which is hard to park at, so just an extra block or 2, if you park here and then head over through the block creek strip entrance near the sports park of Lincoln Avenue. This park also has 2 Nay, check that 3 lovely promenades. 

Speaker 1  (01:19)
These are Nice little mini parts that stretch out to the end of firevista and overlook Lincoln boulevard into the lovely lovely veyones, wetlands, which is the second largest open space in Los Angeles County, New York City. Check that fact. And it is not really accessible, and there are a few trails that we're allowed to walk on other than that. 

Speaker 1  (01:47)
It's a closed ecological preserve, which is left for the birds, as they say, even to the birds. It's a beautiful style and these vistas have such amenities as benches and telescopes for bird spotted. So you can look out on the wetlands and see the migrating sea birds and various 

Speaker 2  (02:09)
Birds that come hither. It's the largest wetlands remaining wetlands stopover for migratory birds that remains in this part of the country. So it's very, very protective, very beautiful space worth a look coming out to these hats. 

Speaker 1  (02:25)
I love the viewpoints one of them even has a one of them even has an oversized hammock to lie on. 

Speaker 2  (02:36)
There's all sorts of loads. 

Speaker 1  (02:36)
Federal jammers around the concert park area. Each little arm kind of going off towards either by a Vesta boulevard on the east side or Lincoln on the west side. 

Speaker 2  (02:49)
It has little hidden parts 

Speaker 1  (02:50)
You may discover something new, like a hammock to sit in or a kid's structure to climb on, it's worth a look. 
