
Speaker 1  (00:00)
Now we come to the playonas discovery part, which is a lovely part that is set up in conjunction with the friends of Beyoncé. Wetland's ecological preserve and sumpia vista organization dropped the checkout on which ones are in responsible for that. The friends of bionus maintain it, and it shows all the native plants that can grow in this area. 

Speaker 1  (00:23)
And it talks about the aboriginals people who live here and it talks about the bluffs and the dangers to the ecosystem, cactuses and animals and the birds that are always flying around here, and it just has lots of informational stuff kind of please touch museum style, exhibits kids love that has blocks to climb. On and benches to sit in dog bags to collect your dog materials, picnic gathering areas. But really? 

Speaker 1  (00:55)
It feels like a very nice woodsy park with nature trails, running through it. And so many plants that never really has like that open Picnic Area. Feel has very nice infinite feeling to it and it's very compact, right on the other side of this. 

Speaker 1  (01:11)
The elementary and it is I don't know how large it is, but it's very compact. And it also has a nice sculpture and honor of the tongue of people from the village of guashna, the first people who lived on this land so, you know, they're really representing out here as well as the parallel bars for all those who are working on the world tour. This is a stop on the world tour where you can work your arms out and do some dips and do some bar walks or maybe some gymnastics, if that's where you're going for and it's quite a nice nice little park. 
