
Speaker 1  (00:00)
Now, we come through hammock lane, little split park that happens right here, just between some condos. And it's just a really beautiful spot and this is also where we can find little statue of little Barry Allen burkis, this is a little relief sculpture of all the plia vista and his shoes and his studying materials and just little memorial to him, the founder, the creator of developer of clivista. This is just one of the secret gardens applied Vesta. 

Speaker 1  (00:35)
Another lovely Scott to visit very, very nice. 
