
Speaker 1  (00:00)
Second, stop on the tour is here at What is this park called? Glenn Greenwood dog park forget. And it's the dog park across the street from home depot, but it's hidden by hedges. 

Speaker 1  (00:19)
So it's still in ply a visto on that side of the hedge, and you have to access it through this little loop road that comes around here. So it's always quite empty, and it's a nice little secret dog park. And yeah, there's many vengeance to sit on and next to this. 

Speaker 1  (00:39)
Smart playground for children. If you have a child, you wanna bring them to God, this would be, you know, possibility. 

Speaker 2  (00:48)
Stuff and there's street parking here, which is free. 

Speaker 1  (00:51)
So maybe this is a good place to start your pie just still walk and not have to worry about the other more busy parking right now. So 
