
Speaker 1  (00:06)
Yes, this is another excellent. Stop on the tour phone TV trail. Which features more world tour workout equipment? 

Speaker 1  (00:15)
The famous setup bench, as well as several outlet balconies that jut over the wetlands so that you can stand there and feel like you're in the middle of the wetlands, right along the bluff creek, and there's birds and an evening frogs or croky. And it's just a really, really lovely environment, and If you walk up through here, and this is where the first victim of the pickleball wars has struck and the theater. Park tennis court was replaced by a permanent pickleball court. 

Speaker 1  (00:51)
There was no more tennis to be found near the overrider dog park. And here we have what I call the happiest place on earth. The overrider dog park, because well, it just makes me happy to go there and see all my dog friends and my dog loves it too, and that's where Reese goes. 

Speaker 1  (01:11)
And get his socializing in And That's the end of this overrider dog park plus pickleball court + 2 court basketball courts section. I'm not sure if this park has another name, but we'll just call it the overrider park with the overrider dog park within 
