
Speaker 1  (00:00)
This is also the start of the playa vista side of the bluff creek trail loop, which goes all the way up to the Avalon. I mean, the annuburg pet space and loops around up onto the LMU bluff off to Lincoln and then back down and into the sports park, and that trail is just a lovely trail. And along, that trail is the world. 

Speaker 1  (00:21)
Trail from world from play world systems, which has such like excellent outdoor workout systems as the step up routine, providing stools and a bar to balance on and step up on or a nice metal bench that provides you with place to put your feet when you're doing sit-ups, or it also has a Pole. To lean against, you know, all sorts of Poles and benches to workout on with instructions is beginner, media and advanced level options for all of those world. Tour world sports tour. 

Speaker 1  (01:00)
John's that they have here. 
