
Speaker 1  (00:01)
The sports park. This is one of why vests other jewels, providing a large pool size competition soccer field with artificial turf? That's just maintained beautifully as well as it's already prepainted for 2 other full size halfway across each half soccer courts for youth soccer and smaller events, and it can even be partitioned in the 4 soccer fields. 

Speaker 1  (00:30)
I believe has a lot of different painting on there that I'm not exactly familiar with. To be honest, it also has a baseball diamond, a large play structure with all these lovely musical instruments that the kids can Bang on and make all sorts of noises and sounds. And creative outlets, and it's quite noisy. 

Speaker 1  (00:50)
So if you don't want to be near noises like that, maybe best to avoid it, there's also 3 bathrooms, all of them multisexual. So anyone can go into any of those bathrooms. And tennis courts, there's 2 tennis courts here, the last holdouts of the pickleball wars. 

Speaker 1  (01:08)
These ones are still tennis, courts and holdings strong Pick was replaced many of the tennis court's empire. Vista plus about forward basketball court here, as well as prior vista elementary LA unified school district public school sits on the corner of the sports park. This park is located on Lincoln boulevard and plya Vesta boulevard, right on the corner. 

Speaker 1  (01:32)
And it's also a great place to walk your dog again as everywhere is around flights. Because there's trails going through it. And this trail on the south side of it meanders beautifully right along the bluff creek below the loyal Manora mount university bluff, and this is an extension of the bianas wetlands and it's prohibited to enter for a foot traffic unless you are working as part of the ecological preserve. 

Speaker 1  (02:01)
So it's very protected area again is often many, many migrating and nesting birds. Songbirds to great-great place for birders, the birders to they flock here like Hertz, and you also are across the street from the ecological preserve across Lincoln, the large bayonets, wetlands ecological preserve. So it's a really just central hub. 

Speaker 1  (02:29)
It also has the largest free parking lot in pia vista and it's just often totally packed. Because it has the soccer field. So if there's any kind of you know, sporting event going on, then it's not the parking lot to go for and that's when you would look around and press and park, perhaps as a good backup plan for your parking for this. 
