
Speaker 1  (00:09)
Now we come to the lawn. Now we come to the lawn, a playoff vista Standby right in the middle of the runway. The runway is play a vistas outdoor mall, which has a Whole Foods, a CVS, a large shopping center and Cedar Sinai many fine restaurants, dance studios, bike rentals, bike sales, all sorts of stuff. 

Speaker 1  (00:37)
That's a pretty pretty big little mall, pretty big little mall and yeah, this park is called the lawn. And it's just like right across from The runway makes sense and it has 2 sides to it on both sides in the street. One side is grass, and one side is hard roughicial turf. 

Speaker 1  (00:56)
One side is in between stops and actually hidden. To begin. It is an outside Corner of millennium. 

Speaker 1  (01:09)
Town center ground isn' This is your park to Send appointed focuses for any kind of commercial activity going on by vista and yeah, and we're also right next to the resort. Which is also a millennium down, on the other side of McConnell Avenue, and the resort is another one of the private facilities of biovista, which has an indoor pool A. Gym, and many other amenities that I can't tell you about. 

Speaker 1  (01:37)
Because I'm not privy through the access of the interior spaces of the resorts. 
